hotelguide.com 2006-09-05

# hotelguide.com Privacy Statement

hotelguide.com Privacy Statement
hotelguide.com respects your individual privacy. We have therefore adopted this Privacy Policy
that represents our commitment to the protection of your privacy. hotelguide.com is the sole
owner of the information collected on this site. We do not, and in the future will not, sell your
personally identifiable information to anyone.
Because we take protecting your privacy seriously hotelguide.com provides the following to policy
to explain our online practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is
collected and used.
      •  When you become a registered user of hotelguide.com you provide your name, address,
         telephone number, email address, a unique login name, password and you can choose to
         provide credit card details. This information is stored for your convenience so you won’t
         have to re-enter that information each time you make a reservation. It also ensures we
         are then able to make and confirm your hotel reservations. We do not share this personal
         information with outside parties except where necessary (i) to complete your reservation
         and/or (ii) to provide our affiliate partners, through whose website you may accessed
         hotelguide.com, with reports listing the hotel bookings made via such affiliate partner’s
         website.
      •  Your contact information is also needed to notify you in the event of any processing
         difficulties or unforeseen circumstances.
Log files:
      •  We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements, and
         gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to
         personally identifiable information.
      •  IP addresses may also be used to help diagnose problems with our servers and for
         general system administration.
Security:
When you make a hotel reservation, or access your registered user profile, we offer the use of a
secure server. The Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology encrypts all information you input
before it is sent to our server.
Newsletters:
hotelguide.com’s newsletters (if applicable) are optional extras for registered users of
hotelguide.com to keep you up to date with our latest news and offers. We hope you will find
these updates useful and interesting. At any time you can unsubscribe to these newsletters
through your account links on our homepage or by contacting: service@hotelguide.com.
On-line Surveys:
hotelguide.com values opinions and comments from our registered users, so from time to time we
conduct surveys. These are optional for users and the information is aggregated and used to
make improvements to hotelguide.com, develop interesting content, features and promotions for
our registered users. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.
Affiliates:
An affiliate is a website not owned by or operated by hotelguide.com, but uses hotelguide.com’s
data and booking capabilities for processing hotel reservations. The hotelguide.com name may or
may not appear on the Affiliate site.
You may have accessed hotelguide.com via one of our Affiliate websites. We may share
personally identifiable information with the respective Affiliate partner by providing it with reports
listing the hotel bookings made via such Affiliate partner’s website. Hotelguide.com is not,

however, responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites. We encourage you to read the
privacy statement of the Affiliate and each and every website you visit that collects personally
identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the
hotelguide.com website.
Current Delivery Partners:
hotelguide.com is partnered with OANDA to provide visitors with a currency calculator and
converter. hotelguide.com is also a partner of Vicinity to deliver an interactive mapping facility. No
personal information or information about patterns or usage is shared between hotelguide.com
and OANDA or Vicinity.
hotelguide.com is also partnered with Amadeus (Central Reservation System) to carry out online
bookings of hotels. Your personal information is shared with this company for purpose of
completing your hotel reservation and will not be used for any other purpose, unless disclosed in
this Privacy Policy
Notification of changes:
Any material changes in the way hotelguide.com uses personal information will be described in
future versions of this Privacy policy. We will always post changes at
www.hotelguide.com/privacy.html so you can keep up to date with what information we collect,
how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any we disclose it. If you have any concerns
about this policy or our privacy practices send them to service@hotelguide.com (referring to
privacy policy in the subject) and we will attempt to respond as soon as possible.
